DC School Newspapers
DC Public Library, Special Collections
DC School Newspapers Collection
1936-2002
DC Public Library, Special Collections
2 linear feet; 2 boxes
117
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, June 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life (2 copies), 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, September 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - McKinley High School - Tech Life, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ballou High School - Ballou Charter, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ballou High School - Ballou Charter, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ballou High School - Ballou Charter, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Benjamin Banneker High School - Train of Thought, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cardozo High School - The Cardozo Owl, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Central High School - The Central Bulletin, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - The Coolidge Courier, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - Colt Pride, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Calvin Coolidge High School - Colt Pride, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - McKinley Manual Training School - Hand and Mind, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - McKinley Manual Training School - Hand and Mind, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - McKinley Manual Training School - Hand and Mind, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Spingarn High School - The Sentinel, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Washington Business High School - The Orange and Blue, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Washington Business High School - The Balance Sheet, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Washington Business High School - The Balance Sheet, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 41)